麦琪:在上一集的中……
Maggie: Previously on growing pains...
杰森:没有,
Jason: No, I just told all of them clean out their houses of the unwanted
我只是说他们可以将房子里的废品清理出去卖给废品收理站,
junk, then they could sell them on the garage sale.
这样我们的房间也就干净了.
That way we get a clean house.and they get ......
麦琪:接着他们就拿到钱了.
Maggie: Then they get to keep all the money.
杰森:他们只拿一半,因为这个是我的提议.
Jason: Half.That was my idea.
本:嘿!这椅子上怎么有个脸?哇,这真是个漂亮的烟灰缸,
Ben: Wow, what's the beautiful ashtray I made to dad doing out here?
爸爸怎么会把他扔在这里?爸爸这是个怪人,他很喜欢这个烟灰缸的,他还曾说这是他所收到的最漂亮的礼物!
Dad was freak.He said it was the best present he's ever got.
迈克:那是他在说谎.
Mike: He was lying.
本:嘿!难道你觉得烟灰缸有感情吗?
Ben: Don't you think ashtray has feelings, too?
迈克:我只是想说这伙计受伤啦!
Mike: I want to say I do, this puppet is in some pain.
杰森:这是你送给我最好的生日礼物.
Jason: It's the best present I've got from you.
开萝尔:本,把那个放下,我们现在去搬地下室里的东西.
Carol: Ben, put that down, we should have taken out all that junk in basement.
本:对不起,烟灰缸.
Ben: Sorry, ashtray.
烟灰缸:你是有些不对,伙计.
Ashtray: You are sorry, pal.
本:你好吗?可怜的烟灰缸?
Ben: Hello?Hello?Heard you, ashtray?
开萝尔:本,快来!
Carol: Ben, come on.
烟灰缸:这孩子从一堆泥土里把我捏了出来.用了几年后就碎了,接着我们就被丢进了垃圾堆.
Ashtray: The kid wards me from lump of clay, breaks Mike and me and Ben
a couple of years later on garbage
运动鞋:然后你就发臭了.
Sneakers: That stinks.
眼镜:不,那是你.
Glasses: No, but you.
迈克:让我猜猜,这是开萝尔的眼镜?
Sneakers: Let me guess, You are Carol's glasses.
眼镜:我知道你是迈克的运动些.这可以从空气中闻出来.
Glasses: You are mike's sneaker.I can feel it in the air.
迈克:我该怎么说呢?你得了多少分就是多少分.
Mike: What can I say why I can do it?When you got it, you
got it
开萝尔:嘿!我的旧眼镜怎么在这里?
Carol: Hey, what are my old glasses doing out here?
本:你不是再也不用它了吗?所以我……
Ben: Well, you'll never wear it any more?So I...
开萝尔:你想错了.
Carol: Your thinking is wrong.
本:那我也想留着我的烟灰缸.
Ben: Well, I do want to keep my ashtray.
开萝尔:为什么?
Carol: Why?
本:因为它还是像新的一样.
Ben: Well, it's still good.It's new.
开萝尔:的确是的.
Carol: It sure is.
烟灰缸:谢谢,本,谢谢你.
Ashtray: Thank you, Ben, thank you.
开萝尔:哦,本,这下好了,看来我们是再也不可能把这买出去了.
Carol: Now, great, Ben.Now we can't even sell it.
迈克:本,这些东西你怎么不扔掉,还要去粘补干什么?
Mike: Ben, why don't you just toss that thing, get it out of its misery.
本:迈克,这种胶水特别好用,你不记得了吗?
Ben: Mike, this goofy glue works miracles.Remember?
台灯:哈……
Lamp: Ha...
迈克:是谁?
Mike: Who's that?
本:你也听到了.
Ben: You heard it too.
开萝尔:你们能不能过来帮个忙?
Carol: Would you guys give me a hand?
迈克:好的.
Mike: Yeah.
台灯:你现在感觉如何?
Lamp: How are you feeling?
烟灰缸:除了头有点痛,其他都还好.
Ashtray: Oh, aside from a splitting head, I go ok.
你知到生活就是这样的.
You know, just when you think life can get worse, it does.
帽子:当然是这样的.这是个冰冷,肮脏和恐怖的世界.
Hat: Of course, it does.It's a cold, ugly, horrible world.Well...
烟灰缸:你没事吧?
Ashtray: You are ok?
帽子:我是有点老了,但我还活着.
Hat: I am an old hat; I live.
迈克:嘿!
Mike: Hi.
特里:嘿!
Terry: Hi.
特里:你也是新来的?
Terry: Are you new here too?
迈克:是的,今天是第一天.
Mike: Yes, the first day.
特里:我是第二天,我还没想的这有怎么复杂的.
Terry: It's my second.I don't know it's all so complex.
迈克:你是在说笑吗?
Mike: You are kidding?
特里:卡拉斯纳·斯科特说要是我能好好工作,
Terry: Mr.Krasner Scooter says if I really apply myself,
我就可能成为像乔·斯卡尤里奥那样的优秀员工.
I can get to be an employee of the month, just like the Joey Scayuglio.
迈克:你还蛮有抱负的.
Mike: Dare to dream.
女顾客:来有一份大的奶酪汉堡,一些炸薯条和一杯黑啤的那种套餐.
Girl buyer: Titanic Cheese Burger, considerable fries and a Woo beer, a diet quota.
迈克:你是和我说话吗?
Mike: Talk to me?
女顾客:是的,大哥.
Girl buyer: Oh, brother.
迈克:没问题,我马上给你拿,好吗?
Mike: No, I now swear on this, ok.
女顾客:这是大号的,我说的是特大号的.
Girl buyer: That's a colossal.I said a Woo.
迈克:哦,对不起.
Mike: Oh, right, sorry.
迈克:好了,一杯咖啡不加糖,一只奶酪汉堡加生菜,一包炸土豆片,两杯冰茶,一杯特大的,另一杯大号的,还有一个花色冰激凌圣代.
Mike: Ok.That's one Mad House no nuts, one Titanic Burger, hold the ice burg lettuce, with one considerable fries, two ice teas, one Woo, one colossal no ice, one patti melt-down with nuclear dressing.Fries on the side.
杰森:我知道他会干得挺好的,快看!
Jason: I knew it was right...Look at him go.
迈克:谢谢光临,欢迎提出意见.这真是是幸福的一家,欢迎光临汉堡包餐厅,要我效劳吗?
Mike: Nine and ten.Thank you and as we say at WOB, don't get any onion.What a charming little family here.Welcome to the World of Burgers!How may
I help you
杰森:谢谢,我们只是来看看.
Jason: Well, we just came to look.
迈克:好吧,爸爸,你想点些什么吃的吗?
Mike: Well, you got to order something, Dad.
本:好的,我要一些鱼.
Bike: Ok.I'll take a meal on a stick...
麦琪:你不能吃那些垃圾食品.
Maggie: No, you don't.No junk food.
迈克:妈妈!
Mike: Mom...
麦琪:今晚家里已经烧好菜了,我可不想他回去吃不下了.
Maggie: We had a nice dinner already at home.I don't want him loading up
on grease
开萝尔:不用多久,他就会被解雇的.
Carol: Double or nothing, he's out of here in 10 minutes.
杰森:迈克,你是我们家的第一位优秀员工,
Jason: Mike, we've just never have an employee of the month in our family.
我们只是来看看你工作的.
We just came down to see you work.
麦琪:迈克,我一直对穿制服的男人有好感的.
Maggie: I've always been a sucker for a man in uniform.
杰森:啊,你有好感?
Jason: Yeah, you have?
麦琪:迈克.我们为你准备了一个小小的惊喜.
Maggie: Mike, we have a little surprise for you.
杰森:是的,一个小惊喜.
Jason: Oh, a little surprise.
麦琪:不管怎么样,你下班后就直接回家好吗?
Maggie: Anyway.Be sure you come straight home after work.OK?
迈克:好的.
Mike: Ok.
斯科特:嘿!我是这里的经理,现在这里有问题吗?
Scooter: Hi!I'm the manager.Is there a problem here?
杰森:不,没有.
Jason: No, none whatsoever.
早上我来这里吃早餐,这个年轻人的服务相当令我满意.
I was down here for breakfast this morning,
所以现在我带全家来看看他.
and this young man gave me such incredible service.
那现在,孩子们,
I just wanted to bring the whole family down to meet him in person.
我们该走了,但我们得牢牢记住今天这样的日子.
So kids, we'd better be going.But, I want you to remember this day, always.
特里:迈克,我不知道要做些什么?
Terry: Mike, I don't know what to do.This guy wants extra ketchup.
那个家伙老是问我要调料,我没法让他离开.
I tried to talk him out of it.
迈克:特里,你不用那么紧张.
Mike: Terry, Terry, would you just relax.
特里:我没法不紧张,要是搞糟了,我就会被解雇的.
Terry: I can't relax.Mike, if I mess up again I'm out of here?
迈克:你不会搞糟的,是吧?
Mike: You're not gonna mess up, Ok?
斯科特:特里,你的收银柜怎么还开着?
Scooter: Terry!Your register draw is open!
迈克:哦,斯科特,
Mike: Ah, look, Scooter.That's my fault.
那是我开的.
Since you just came back from a break and I was handling both registers
她刚刚去洗手间了,是我开了忘关的.
while she was gone.
斯科特:迈克?你是怎么会成为优秀员工的?
Scooter: Mike?I, I, I don't believe it!You're the employee of the month!
迈克:是的,对不起.
Mike: Yeah, look, I'm sorry.
斯科特,
Scooter, look, I have learned my lesson,
我会吸取教训的,你知道我现在紧张的要命.
my heart is just beating a mile a minute here.
特里:哦,迈克,
Terry: Huh, Mike.That was so nice of you.
你真是太好了.要是以后有什么需要我帮忙的,你尽管讲.
If there is ever anything I could ever do for you, don't hesitate to ask, Ok?
迈克:好的.
Mike: Well...
斯科特:迈克!
Scooter: Mike!
迈克:是的,斯科特.
Mike: Oh, yes, Scooter!
斯科特:怎么还少37美元!
Scooter: This cash register is 37 dollars short!
迈克:37美元!
Mike: 37!
斯科特:我真不知道该说什么好!
Scooter: I, I, I, I just don't know what to say.
迈克:对不起,斯科特先生,这事不会有第二次的.
Mike: Look, Scooter, I'm sorry.It will not happen again.
斯科特:我知道了.
Scooter: I know.
迈克:被炒了!爸爸?今天发生什么事了?
Mike: Ah, fired!Mom, Dad?Dad something's happened today?
大伙:惊奇一下吧!
All: Surprise!
麦琪:这是为我们的优秀员工准备的.
Maggie: A little something for our employee of the month.
杰森:迈克,我们为你骄傲!
Jason: Mike, we're so proud of you!
迈克:我并不非要他们一定得相信我,
Mike: I, I didn't ask them to have faith in me, did I, right?
对吧?
Yes or no?
本:不.
Ben: Um, no.
迈克:那就好了.
Mike: That's right.
本:好的.
Ben: Good.
迈克:他们应该知道我是如何把事弄糟的,对吧?
Mike: They should know I'm gonna find a way to mess things up, right?
我也不知是怎么回事?
What's the problem?
本:你又弄糟了?
Ben: You messed up?
迈克:不!
Mike: No!
本:哦.
Ben: Oh.
迈克:这不是我的错,但是能女孩难过吗?
Mike: I mean.I'm not about to go in there and break their little hearts.
我是不能那样做的,是吧?本.
I can't do something like that.Can I, Ben?
本:当然能.
Ben: Sure.
迈克:不!
Mike: No!
本:那才是我的想法.
Ben: Ah, that's what I meant.
迈克:那么看来只能是靠我自己解决了.
Mike: So, now I have to do what I have to do.
本:是的.
Ben: Right.
迈克:你看,本,要是你想生活的轻松一点,就别让爸爸妈妈对你有太高的期望,我现在左右为难啊!(音乐响起,迈克在寻找新工作.)
Mike: Look, Ben.If you want to save yourself a lot of grief, don't let mom and dad expect great things from you.Let them know your a real disappointment now. (music  Mike try to find a new work)
杰森:喂?
Jason: Hello?
特里:嘿!我是特里,迈克在家吗?
Terry: Hi!I'm Terry, is Mike home?
麦琪:没有.
Maggie: No.
特里:他的制服在家吗?
Terry: Is his burger uniform home?
麦琪:没有,他正穿着呢.
Maggie: No, he's wearing it.
特里:那太糟了!
Terry: Oh, that is so sad.
杰森:特里,我是精神病医生.
Jason: Terry, I'm a psychiatrist.
特里:我是汉堡餐厅新的经理助理,
Terry: Well, I, I'm the new assistant manager at World of Burgers,
我得要穿他的制服.
and I need his uniform.
杰森:但迈克也要穿呀!
Jason: Oh, well, Mike needs it.
特里:干什么用?
Terry: For what?
杰森:工作呀!
Jason: For work.
特里:那很好,他被解雇的时候,我真是为他难过.
Terry: That's great!I felt so bad when he got fired.Well,
杰森:等会.
Jason: Hold it!
特里:等什么?
Terry: Hold what?
杰森:迈克被解雇了?
Jason: Mike was fired?
迈克:嘿!爸爸.
Mike: Hey Dad!
杰森:这不是我那日夜辛苦工作的好儿子吗?
Jason: Well, if it isn't my hard working son and his well deserved car?
迈克:是啊,爸爸,你知道今天有多忙吗?
Mike: Yeah, that's us, Dad.You know I'm really bushed today, Dad.
杰森:那你又是怎么被他们解雇的?
Jason: So how you go down at the World of Burgers?
看来你是有些麻烦!
Looks like you got some onion.
迈克:好吧,爸爸,我就把实情告诉你吧!
Mike: Yeah, well, to tell you the truth, Dad.
杰森:对不起,什么?
Jason: Excuse me, the what?
迈克:我就把实情告诉你吧!怎么说呢?
Mike: Tell you the truth.
我已经不是那家汉堡店的员工好几天了.
Ah, I don't know, I'm getting a little bummed with WOB.
杰森:哦,但你是那里的有些员工呀!
Jason: Oh, but you're the employee of the month.
迈克:是的,你知道那里的压力很大的,
Mike: Yeah, you know, there's a lot of pressure there, dad, and I don't know.
爸爸,怎么说呢?
They are talking about making me an assistant manager.
他们说会升我为经理助理,
That would mean I'd have to go to burger college and I just don't know
还要送我到大学进修,但你知道我不是上大学的料.
if I'm university material.
杰森:你是想说你就是因为这个就把工作辞了.
Jason: So you're telling me that you're considering quitting this job?
迈克:是的,我已经找到了另一份好工作了,
Mike: Well, I've already got a better job to lined up, Dad.
是一家汽车公司.
Yes, in the auto-motive industry.
杰森:哦!是福特?通用?还是克莱斯勒?
Jason: Ah!Ford?General motors?Crysler?
迈克:伯尼
Mike: Burney.
杰森:伯尼?
Jason: Burney?
迈克:是的,是伯尼汽车清洗公司.
Mike: Yeah, Burney's car wash.I want to be a rag man, Dad.
爸爸,我现在是一名汽车清洗工了,
Tips galore and a great future.Oh, I can't do this.
那里的待遇和前途都不错.好吧!爸爸,
I can't look you in the face and lie.
我不能再骗你了,你是不是有看穿我的魔力.
What is it, some kind of magic power?
杰森:迈克,我……
Jason: Mike, I have...
迈克:爸爸,我是被解雇了.
Mike: Dad, I got fired.Ok, it wasn't even my fault.
但爸爸,这不是我的错.
Dad, I mean, I was covering for this girl named Terry who left her register
当时一个叫特里的女孩因为收银柜开着把钱丢了,我为了保护她,就说那是我开的.
draw open.Sorry, I wanted to tell you but I guess that was the day you
当时你送我车的时候我就想告诉你的,但我不知道怎么跟你讲.
gave me this car.What was I supposed to say then?
杰森:是的,你是不想失去车子.
Jason: Oh, yes.You didn't want to risk losing the car.
迈克:哦,爸爸.
Mike: Oh, dad.It wasn't because of the car.
这不是因为车,
I mean, it was, but not the way you mean.
那是因为我已经没脸见你们,
It was just such a new experience, I mean,
你们这么称赞我,而我又让你们蒙羞了.
how could you be so proud of me?It confused me.
杰森:是的,现在我也没脸见你.
Jason: Well, it confused me, too.
迈克:那你现在不是见我了吗?爸爸.
Mike: So don't you see, dad?
我只是希望你别把我看成一个失败者,
I mean, I just didn't want you to think I was some loser who couldn't
一个一点责任心也没有的人,我希望你对我有点信心.
be trust with any responsibility.Just when you started having faith in me.
杰森:好的,但你首先你要对自己有信心.
Jason: Well, you've got to have a little faith in me, too.
迈克:得了,爸爸,
Mike: Oh, come on, dad, no.
如果你发现我解雇了,
If you had somehow found out that I was fired, you'd be out here pacing,
你就会发大火,然后对妈妈说你决不会相信我了.
telling mom how stupid you were to trust me.
杰森:是的,也许我们会这样的.
Jason: Well, possibly we may...
迈克:爸爸,
Mike: Dad, don't you see,
你看我来骗你是有多难吗?
you know how hard it's been for me to keep the truth from you?
杰森:那你还是为了我着想?
Jason: So you lied to me for me?
迈克:是的,我只是不想让你失望,
Mike: Yeah, I just didn't wanna let you down.
而我自己无论怎么样也无所谓.
No matter what happened to me it didn't matter.
杰森:是的,我应该感谢你.
Jason: Well, I appreciate that.
麦琪:迈克?我们都在等你.
Maggie: Michael?We've been waiting for you.
杰森:麦琪,迈克让我告诉你,
Jason: And Maggie, Mike just told me he lost his job at the Burger place
他上星期就已经被那家汉堡餐厅给解雇了.
last week.
麦琪:哦,真的?
Maggie: Oh he did.
杰森:我也和你一样大吃一惊.
Jason: I was shocked.
麦琪:是吗?杰森,他还骗了我们真正一个星期.
Maggie: You were?Jason, he's been lying to us for an entire week!
杰森:是的,所以才说他是个懂事的孩子.
Jason: Yes.Is that a great kid or what?
帽子:自此以后,我就坐在钩子上了,
Hat: Since that time I've been sitting on the hook, now you want to talk,
痛苦的烟灰缸,现在你想谈谈吗?那你到钩子上来坐两年试试看.
pain ashtray?Try sitting two years on the hook.
烟灰缸:我只是想回到杰森的桌上.
Ashtray: I just want to go back on the Jason's desk.
书本:世界上没有什么誓言是亘古变的!
Book: No swear not by the moon in constant moon in monthly changes in
her circled orbit.
帽子:那就是我所需要的.
Hat: This is what I need.
书本:就像白痴讲的故事,讲的是唾沫横飞,
Book: Just a tale told by an idiot full of sound and fruity and signifying
但是内容却很空洞.这和烟灰缸无关.
nothing, no a fancy ashtray.
烟灰缸:为什么每个人都在做弄我?
Ashtray: Why does everybody pick on me?
书本:那是因为你没有生活和爱情.
Book: Because you have not lived or loved.
老师:西沃,我想告诉你一些你肯定会吃惊的东西.但我想在这课堂上,我们都是平等的,所以要是有个莎士比亚的问题让我决定由谁回答时,我会让你回答的.
Teacher: Seavor, I'm gonna say something to you that might shock you.But in this class, I consider you my equal.Well, what I mean is, if I had a question about Shakespeare, and I had a choice of either asking him or you; I'd ask you.
开萝尔:好的,谢谢.
Carol: Well thank you.
老师:这和他们那些人一天到晚训练无关.
Teacher: And it has nothing to do with the fact that they ran around in
问题是现在需要你的帮助,
tights all the time.And the point is, is that I need your help.
本来我是不会来教这课的,
It's no big secret that I wouldn't even be teaching this class, if Mrs.
只是奥布克斯女士得了点病,你懂我的意思吗?
Orbeaux hadn't gone a little bit flaky, if you know what I mean?
但现在班上有个同学的成绩很差,
But there's a kid who's flunking the class,
可能原因在于我,
who shouldn't be and I kind o' blame myself.
所以我想请你能否辅导他一下?
So, I was wondering if, maybe you could tutor him.
开萝尔:好吧,不过我还从没有想过当一个老师呢!
Carol: Well, I've never really thought of myself as a ...teacher.
老师:嘿!谁会想过呢?所以你觉得怎么样?
Teacher: Hey, who has?So what do you say?
开萝尔:好吧,就让我试试.
Carol: Ok, I'll give it a shot.
老师:嘿!鲍比!
Teacher: Ah, yeah.Hey, Bobby!
开萝尔:就那个运动员?
Carol: The jock?
鲍比:是的,教练!
Bobby: Yo, Coach!!
老师:鲍比,现在我叫西沃辅导你关于莎士比亚的学习.
Teacher: Now, Bobby.Seaver here's gonna help you through all that Shakespeare stuff...
鲍比:好的.
Bobby: Alright.
老师:现在,听着,
Teacher: Now, look!You do everything she says, because, if you don't pass,
你要照她要你做的事做,要是你还是不通过考试,
you don't play.And it aint gonna do you no good comin' crying your eyes
你就别想打球了.到时也不要像去年那样缠着我再给你打球的机会.
out to me; like you did last year.
鲍比:我想我们这是第一次见面吧!我叫鲍比·文内特.
Bobby: I don't think we ever really met.I'm Bobby Winette.
开萝尔:我知道.
Carol: I know.
鲍比:那你就是天才开萝尔了.
Bobby: And you're Carol, "The Brain".
开萝尔:我知道,去年你是不是真的哭了?
Carol: I know.You actually cried last year?
鲍比:是的,是大哭了一场.
Bobby: Yeah.Groin pull.
开萝尔:鲍比,我不知道罗密欧在自杀前为什么不给朱丽叶做心脏按摩呢?
Carol: Bobby, I don't know why Romeo didn't try CPR on Juliet before he killed himself.
鲍比,
Bobby: I mean, the guy doesn't even check the pulse,
我想在他自杀前他连朱丽叶的脉搏都没摸过.
before he does himself in.
开萝尔:鲍比,真个剧本是相当古典的,它已经有四百年的历史了.
Carol: Bobby, the play is over four hundred years old.It's a Classic.
鲍比:要是我是罗密欧,你是朱丽叶,
Bobby: If I was Romeo,
而且我真的是很喜欢你的话,
and you were Juliet and I really had it bad for you,
那谁也不可能阻止我去爱你.无论是我的家庭,
there's nothing nobody could say that would get in the way...
还是你的家庭.
not my family, not your family, not nobody.
到人们发现我们已经不在了的时候,我们已经逃到了新泽西.
By the time those people turned around to look for you and me,
对不起,
we'd be in my pick-up, half way to Jersey!!I'm sorry I lost my temper.
我太容易激动了,我想我是个很情绪化的人.
Sometimes my emotions get the best of me.I guess I'm too sensitive.
开萝尔:没关系!反正我也不想教你了.
Carol: It's OK.I really didn't want it anymore, anyway.
鲍比:这个辅导本身就很愚蠢,我毕竟太笨了.
Bobby: This tutoring stuff's a bad idea.My head's too thick.
开萝尔:不不!
Carol: No, no, no, no, no.
要理解莎士比亚的确不是一件容易的事,
Understanding Shakespeare is a very difficult thing to do.
我当初是花了好几个月才读懂他的剧本的.
You know, when I first read his plays I was lost for months;
害的整个六年级的成绩都很差.
it ruined my entire sixth grade year.
鲍比:你六年就开始看他的剧本?
Bobby: You read this stuff in the sixth grade?
开萝尔:我很不可思议吗?
Carol: I'm weird, OK?
鲍比:不不!你很聪明.
Bobby: No, no, no!!You're smart.
你要是来辅导我,你一定会郁闷的.
Boy, spending this much time with me must really be boring for you, huh?
开萝尔:不会那样的,我们讲到哪里了?
Carol: Not really.So where were we?
鲍比:每个人都死了.
Bobby: Everybody was dead.
朋友乙:鲍比怎么回事?
Friend 2: So, like what is this Bobby Winette situation?
开萝尔:没怎么回事,我在辅导他.
Carol: There's no situation, I'm just tutoring him.
朋友:是怎么一回事?
Friend: Oh, well what figures.
开萝尔:你们是什么意思?
Carol: And what is that supposed to mean?
朋友:我怎么知道?
Friend: Well, I don't know.
朋友乙:得了,开萝尔,
Friend 2: Oh, come on Carol, don't have a cow!
你没有出事!大家都知道你们是很纯洁的.
Everybody knows, you're immaculate.
开萝尔:纯洁?
Carol: Immaculate?
朋友:就是很健康,但往往会有些糟糕的事,
Friend: You know, wholesome.Well, there are worse things to be...errm...
譬如肥胖.
like fat.
开萝尔:好吧,
Carol: Well, for your information,
你们听着,鲍比昨晚和我在我的房间里念书,
Bobby and I did our studying all evening in my bedroom.
我们讨论的问题是罗米欧和朱丽叶.
And the subject was "Romeo and Juliet", if you get my meaning.
你们听懂我在讲什么吗?我就是说在学校里我们很规矩,
You know, maybe I don't have to ogle the boys' swim team and act like
但在家就可以随心所欲了.
a little girl, when I can be a woman, at home.
杰森:迈克,你好像打过架里了.
Jason: Mike, you look like you've been in a fight!
迈克:是的.
Mike: Oh yeah!
杰森:和谁呢?
Jason: Well, who with?
迈克:和我那六年级的演讲班.
Mike: My sixth period speech class.
杰森:什么?你和整个班级打架?
Jason: What, you fought the whole class?
迈克:爸爸,那是他们挑起的.
Mike: Look, I don't know Dad, I was at the bottom of the pile.
现在的关键不是打架这件事,也不是我被留校察看的事.
Look, my fight is not important right now, neither is my suspension.
杰森:你被留校察看了?
Jason: You were suspended?
迈克:是的,
Mike: Yeah.Look, alright.
你听我说,
At the start of the class,
当时我刚开始上课,大家就来问我有没有听到新闻.
everybody comes up to me and asks if I've heard the news.
我说什么新闻,
I say, "what news?", "about Carol".
他们说关于是关于开萝尔的.
Well, you know me, I'm always ready for a good Carol nerd story.
我一般是不会在乎他们说开萝尔是书呆子的,
Yeah, and then he starts saying this disgusting stuff about Carol.
但他们这次却说开萝尔是糟糕至极.开始我还笑着以为他们是说着玩的,
So, I keep smiling, you see, and waiting for the punch line;
谁知这是真的.
only he's not kidding.
这下我火了,
And I don't know what happened but the next thing I know,
就打了埃迪一拳,
I was in there punching Eddie out.
于是他们就一起来打我.当时我也不知怎么会发这么大火,
And then I was in there swinging and kicking,
只是想即便大家都来打我,
and I couldn't even figure out why I was so angry.
我也要保护开萝尔.
I'm here I was, getting all busted up, protecting Carol!
麦琪:开萝尔,你怎么会造成这么大坏影响?这件事是不是是个谣言?
Maggie: Carol, how could you start a rumor like that about...It is a rumor, isn't it?
开萝尔:当然,
Carol: Of course it is Mom.
我是说大家都知道纯洁,聪明,
I mean, everybody knows that, decent, responsible,
有责任心的开萝尔是不会做出这种事的.
immaculate Carol wouldn't dare do a thing like that.
麦琪:那为什么会有谣言呢?
Maggie: Then, why?
开萝尔:我不知道.
Carol: I don't know.
麦琪:拿是迈克的回答,我想你能回答的更具体些.
Maggie: Carol, that's a Mike answer.I expect a little more from you.
开萝尔:难道我是圣人?
Carol: What am I, a saint?
你们为什么总是要说:"迈克,
Why do you always have to say, "Mike,
你应该多学学你开萝尔"?
why can't you be more like your sister?"
为什么每次老师离开的时候,
Why does every teacher I've ever had put me in charge,
总让我来管?
when they leave the class room?
还有为什么在学校里每年我都是优秀学生.
Why is it that I'm the one, always to be elected a recording secretary?
麦琪:哦,宝贝,你说的都是些好事.
Maggie: Oh, honey, those are all good things.
开萝尔:我只是在想,
Carol: I just wish, that every once in a while,
我也应该有权力做一回女孩子.
it would be nice to thought of as...dangerous.
麦琪:那他英俊吗?
Maggie: Provocative?
开萝尔:是的.
Carol: Yes.
麦琪:迷人吗?
Maggie: Sexy?
开萝尔:是的.
Carol: Yes.
麦琪:能到你的房间和你一起学习的男生一定不是一般的人,
Maggie: The kind o' girl that should never be allowed to study in her
对吧?
bedroom with a hunk?
开萝尔:是的.
Carol: Yes.
书本:我们是群愚蠢的演员,在台上装疯买傻的直到谢幕.
Book: We are but fool players who until the final curtain draws nigh.
帽子:还是面对生活吧,我们只是些垃圾.
Hat: That's just all face it.We are garbage.
烟灰缸:我不是垃圾.
Ashtray: I am not garbage.
帽子:不,你是肮脏的垃圾.
Hat: No, you are ugly garbage.
开萝尔:哦,这是我的罗米欧和朱丽叶.
Carol: Oh, my copy of Romeo and Juliet.
迈克:是的,这本书已经被你读旧了,不会值多少钱了.
Mike: Yeah, we are not going to get very much for it, 'cause you have read it.
开萝尔:是这本书将鲍比和我连接起来的.
Carol: It a book brought Bob and me together.
迈克:这本书倒是比鲍比强多了
Mike: Then the book do an offer than Bob did.
开萝尔:这书是我以前感情的见证,我是怎么才能让你明白什么叫感情呢?
Carol: It is sentimental of my past.Then how can I expect you to understand sentiment?
迈克:只有没用的人才会谈感情,嘿!我的汉堡店的帽子,你们这帮家伙怎么想的,这些东西都还挺好的,怎么能贱卖呢?
Mike: Look, sentiment is for worms.Hey, my burger hat.What do you guys have
in your minds?You know I let this stuff, pretty good cheap
开萝尔:迈克,这样的话,我们就没什么好卖的啦!
Carol: Mike, this way, we won't have anything left to sell.
迈克:是的,那又怎么样?
Mike: Well, so?
本:是的,因为我要收回我所有的旧东西.
Ben: Good, 'cause I like my all junk.
开萝尔:我想你俩还没有明白废品处理的意义,
Carol: I don't think you two grasp the concept of garage sale...
我跳舞的礼服是绝对不能卖掉的.
My prom dress does not leave this house.
迈克:我想你是对的,爸爸只是想用清理废品买钱的诡计来诱使我们打扫屋子.下次我们应该一开始就要钱.
Mike: You are right I think.Dad telling us about all the money we are
going to make from the garage sale is just his way of tricking us in
cleaning up the house.Next time, we ask for the money of front
本:就像叫一个小孩垃圾并不是说那小孩就是垃圾.
Ben: Just because a garbage pal kid doesn't mean they are garbage.
杰森:迈克,开萝尔,你们可以去卖垃圾了.
Jason: What is Mike and Carol ....they just say the garage sales off.
本:是的,我们什么也不想卖了.
Ben: Yes, we don't want to sell anything.
杰森:这是为什么?
Jason: Why?
本:这样的,爸爸,这些东西令我想起了我的童年.
Ben: Well Dad, this stuff is bringing back memories of my youth.
杰森:是的,但失去这些东西并不是说就失去了你的回忆.
Jason: Yeah, losing something doesn't mean losing your memories.
本:但我还是想留着我的垃圾.
Ben: But I want to keep my all junk.
杰森:那你就留一两件吧,其余的全扔掉.
Jason: Yeah, you get one or two attach all pieces of useless junk that you don't need.
杰森:本,你送我的烟灰缸怎么会在这里?
Jason: Ben, what is this ashtray you gave me doing out here?
本:我不想把它卖了,它原来在箱子里的,
Ben: I didn't want to sell it.It was in a box.
我以为你是不想要了.
I think you just didn't want it any more.
杰森:为什么不要?难道我现在已经戒烟了,烟灰缸就没用了吗?
Jason: Why?Just because I don't smoke, or ever used it.
本:我不懂!
Ben: Yeah.
杰森:好吧,那是讲我还是得要烟灰缸,现在明白了吗?
Jason: Well, That doesn't mean that I don't need it.Well don't you see?
本:没有!
Ben: No.
杰森:也许等你再大一些,你就明白了.现在还是把它放回我的办公室吧!
Jason: Then maybe when you are older.This thing is going right back on my office desk right now.
本:谢谢你,爸爸.
Ben: Thanks, dad.
杰森:我的老友呀!
烟灰缸:你又得到我了.
00:21:19,700
Jason: Nose-clothes. Ashtray: You are controlling me.